the beginning
of the song.
We'll be
right
back to
the beginning of the song.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a big trip, but there's a big thing.
There's a big thing that's there.
I'm sorry, I'll keep you safe.
Okay, let's go ahead and go.
I'm always going to go to the moon.
Hey, somebody go buy some more food!
Yeah, we've got the money.
Get some more booze while you're at it.
When it comes to painting,
I'm in a league of my own.
So, what do you think?
It took all the money.
How can I face the others now, dummy?
All right, guys, it's time to
kick their asses. All of them.
That's it.
Show them.
Looks like you lose this round.
Losers get to go pick up more booze.
Buy all the food they
have in the shop, too.
It's not like we don't have the money.
Be right back.
And when I am, I'm
going to win every hand.
Just you wait.
What was that? What happened?
Who the hell are those guys? You jerks!
You got a death wish?
I recognize him!
It's that pirate!
Straw Hat Luffy!
So you came to get your
money back, did you?
Bad move.
Just take a look around.
Do you really think the four of
you are enough to handle all of us?
But since you're here,
we might as well take those big
bounties you've got on your heads
He's the captain of that long-nosed
weakling we took care of earlier
With that pitiful excuse for a pirate on
his crew, he can't possibly be that strong
Let's go, come on, shrimp
Now come, go!
What do you think you're doing?
Are you punching him?
Not even a bombardment for battleship
cannons can put a den in that armor.
What a joke.
If you're just gonna play around, then
I'll go ahead and end this right now.
And cannon!
He punched a hole right through it!
Hey!
Hold on!
Wait a second, you guys!
Let's talk about this first.
Okay, guys.
Okay, guys, fire the cannons.
Woo-hoo!
Now three-sword style.
Karasu.
Raven hunt.
What?!
Impossible!
Those cannonballs are made of iron!
The cannon's too!
Holy crap!
These guys are seriously bad news!
Let's get out of here!
Everyone run for the back door!
You guys started this fight.
It's kind of pathetic to
run from it like cowards.
Party table kick course!
We can't make it to the back door!
Windows! Use the windows!
Rumble!
More points!
A seal colonnade!
Wait!
You just want the money back.
The 200 million berries the
long-nosed guy had, is that it?
I'm sorry to be the one to tell you, but
that pile of money isn't here anymore.
Franky, the family boss, took it
all and went on a shopping spree.
And since he's buying
something on the black market,
we don't have any idea where he
might be or even how to find him.
So no matter how much of a rampage you go
on, that 200 million won't be coming back.
So why don't you...
DUMBAY!
Shut up.
That's enough out of you.
This has nothing to do with the money.
Damn straight.
It's too late for that.
Not even your bones will
be left when we're done.
Not even our bones?!
What's the matter with you
acting like a bunch of cowards?
We're the Franky family!
We're the ones who do all the
bone-breaking around here!
Got it?
Never forget who you are!
Okay, brothers, let's show them
the specialty of the Franky House!
Now, fire the Anything Shot Cannon!
Here they come! Awesome! Pull it up!
Keep firing till there's
nothing left to shoot!
C'mon!
There's only four of them!
What was that? Fireworks?
Sounds like it's coming from
out toward the Franky house.
Them again?
What trouble are they up to this time?
I know, right?
Hey, quiet, they're gonna hear us.
Oh boy, sounds like they're
getting a little carried away.
When those boys party.
They really don't show any
restraint, now do they?
No big deal.
It's not like they do it all the time.
It's a nice day.
Should we go after Franky?
Start looking. Where?
Oh man.
Looks like these idiots really
didn't know where he took the money.
And if we do find him, if he spent
it, then there's no getting it back.
What now?
Even if we wait around for him, he
may not be back for quite a while.
Okay, the first aid treatment is all done.
We need to take him back on a stretcher
so I can use some help over here.
Hanging around here won't do any good.
Let's head back to the ship for now.
We left Nami there all by herself.
And Robin's still missing.
The ship's a problem, too.
Yeah.
Hey, Luffy!
I've made a decision.
Huh?
About the ship.
It's time to part ways with the Mary.
We'll say goodbye to her here.
All right, then.
We'll be leaving now.
That man is seriously stubborn.
It's infuriating.
We don't even know if he has it or not,
yet they keep sending me out
here, over and over again.
I wish those people would put
themselves in my shoes for once.
It's Khalifa.
Well, come in.
You must be worn out, sir.
Would you like something to drink?
I would, thank you.
Maybe some tea.
I've already prepared it.
Well, I'd expect nothing less
from you. Thank you. I'm grateful.
Poor Mr.
Corgi is always so angry
when he leaves, isn't he?
What in the world does he
come here to talk about?
Oh, that.
Those he represents want something I
have, and they keep making various offers.
It must be something of great
importance, then, isn't it?
Well, maybe so, though I always
deny knowing anything about it.
They really are tiresome people.
Hey!
Usopp's finally awake,
you guys! All right!
Good to hear!
That's one less thing to worry about.
Hey, Usopp!
Robin still isn't back yet.
You know, I ought to punch
you for scaring us like that.
Yeah, no kidding.
Though it looks like you've taken
enough punches already, if you ask me.
What were you thinking,
taking those guys on alone?
You can't just run off and
fight whoever you want.
Oh, that's a good one coming from you.
This wouldn't have happened
if I was strong like you guys.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I'm so ashamed of myself.
I knew how important that money was.
Hey, hey, stop. I get it.
I know you're sorry, but you don't have
to get all touchy-feely on me, okay?
All our savings, all the trouble we went
through, what about the Mary? Take it easy.
You shouldn't be out of bed yet.
Come on, calm down.
Stop your whining and
listen to the doctor.
So, is there a chance we might
get our money back after all?
Well, maybe.
We won't know for sure till
that Franky guy shows up.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Hey,
even if we can't get the rest back,
we still have a hundred
million berries left over.
Don't worry.
Yeah, but he lost twice that much.
Mommy.
Sorry, Usopp.
No, it's fine.
More importantly, is
Mary going to be okay?
I mean, can we get her repaired
with the money that we have left?
We're lucky we have all these
awesome shipwrights to work on her,
but I know things are going
to get rough out there?
so I want her to be
stronger than ever before.
We aren't having them repair it.
We decided to get a new ship instead.
I know that we probably should have asked
you first, but we didn't have much choice.
Either way, I've made up my mind.
The Going Mary has taken good care of us,
but it looks like our journey
with her has to end here.
Anyway, Ice Pops gave us this
awesome ship catalog to flip through.
There's all kinds of different
ships we could pick from in here.
And if we decided to
shop for a used model?
We could go bigger than the Mary!
and still keep our budget
under $100 million.
Wait.
Just stop.
I get it, Luffy.
But the joke's gone on
long enough, okay? See?
Chopper doesn't know you're kidding.
Look how upset this is making him.
Jeez, Captain, you should know better
than to treat your crew like that.
Come on, Nami, back me up here.
Hold up.
Does that mean we don't
have enough for the repairs?
It's because I lost the
$200 million, isn't it?
And now we can't afford
the work on the Mary.
Is that what this is about?
After all, a first-class shipyard
is going to cost a lot, right?
Would you stop and listen to me?
What is it tell me don't
try to sugarcoat it.
I'm not okay.
I don't even care that you lost
all the money That's over now.
That's how you feel then.
What's with all this crap
about buying a new ship of you?
Stop it fighting isn't gonna help
Just calm down for a sec.
I Don't see what I'm doing wrong.
He's the one saying all
this dumb stuff I know how
you feel but you shouldn't
get so worked up right now.
Listen to Nami Usopp if you don't get
any rest you're not gonna get better!
Who cares about me?
How can you just sit here when he's
making jokes about getting a new ship?
I'm not joking about anything!
This was a hard decision for me, too!
Oh yeah, I feel really sorry for you!
Already window shopping for a new toy!
You trying to pick a fight with me?
I don't want your damn pity, got it?
If you tell me it doesn't
matter that I lost the money,
then why are you talking
about buying a new ship?
Just spit it out already!
If we can't afford the repairs
because I screwed up, then tell me!
Don't show me some stupid
catalog and change the subject!
I want to know the truth!
The Mary can't be...
What?
What did you just say?
Don't make me repeat myself.
I told you, the Mary
can't be repaired anymore.
No matter what we do, we...
we can't fix it.
Otherwise, I wouldn't
say something like that.
You mean this ship?
The ship that we're riding
on right now is broken?
That's right.
It's only a matter of
time before she sinks.
What are you talking
about, Luffy? That's nuts.
No, I'm serious.
The shipwrights took a look
at the Mary themselves.
They said she wouldn't even
hold out until the next island.
And it's settled, so that's it?
A bunch of strangers
tell you to scrap your
ship and you don't even ask any questions?
That's enough!
I understand these guys know what they're
talking about, but this is just wrong!
Don't give up on the Mary!
What about all the adventures
we've gone on together?
What about all the battles we've fought?
She's our friend!
She's one of us!
Are you going to abandon her for
another ship without a second thought?
After all we've been through, is that
how little the Mary means to you, Luffy?
I know you're upset, Usopp,
but you need to calm down.
Sorry, but no.
I'm not pecking down until we settle this.
Usopp, please.
What?
So you know better than the shipwrights?
If we had someone on the crew
who knew about this stuff,
we wouldn't have asked
them in the first place!
Then forget them!
We don't need those guys
telling us what to do!
I'll repair the Mary
myself, just like before!
We've made it this far, so there's
no reason we can't go on that way!
Here, I'll get started right now!
Come on, guys, help me out!
That's not gonna work!
That's right, we don't
have enough lumber, do we?
I better go buy some at the shipyard.
We've got a lot of work to do.
You're not a shipwright, Usopp!
You hear me?
Stop it, Luffy!
Yeah, you're right.
I know.
But so what?
I don't see why you're so hung up on
everything those stupid shipwrights say.
If they knew what she'd gone through,
they wouldn't give up on the Mary so easy.
They just want your money. Usopp?
The Mary's our ship,
so it's our job to take care of her
without someone else butting in.
I'm not giving up.
I won't let them take
the Mary away from me.
This is stupid
You got fooled by a bunch of salesmen
trying to pawn off a used boat.
Luffy I know wouldn't cave in to some
sales bitch from a total stranger!
He'd believe in the strength of the
Mary and the strength of his crew.
But here you are acting like you know
everything and ignoring your friends?
I can't believe that's the kind
of captain you turned out to be.
I thought you were better than that!
You're not being fair, Usopp.
Luffy felt the...
You stay out of this!
It was my call.
I stand by it!
There's nothing you can do.
We're getting a new ship,
whether you like it or not.
This is the end of the road for the Mary.
I'm not leaving her here.
I don't care what you say.
I know you're always trying
to think about the future,
but not everyone on
this crew is like that.
I see the Mary as one
of our friends, got it?
And I won't abandon her when she's hers.
Don't be stupid.
Even if she is a friend, that
doesn't mean she's a person.
She is to me, and she still
has the strength to live!
But you wouldn't appreciate that,
because all you care about is
getting a new ship to play with!
All right, that's enough, both of you.
Stop being so selfish and
think about your crew!
Dude, listen to yourself!
Luffy, don't act like you're the
only one who's torn up about this!
We all feel the same way!
If that was true, then you
wouldn't be looking for a new ship!
All right, fine!
If you don't like the way
your captain does things,
then why don't you go ahead and get on...
Sanji!
This is going way too far.
What the hell is wrong with you?
If you don't watch it,
you're going to say something you
can't take back, so calm down!
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I don't know what I was thinking.
You don't have to apologize, because
that's how you really feel, isn't it?
That's not true!
Just get rid of your dead weight and
move on before they can slow you down.
If you're going to throw away the
Mary, might as well throw me away too.
I know you're pissed off, but
don't say stupid crap like that.
No, I'm serious.
I've been thinking about
this for a while now.
It isn't like it was before.
You guys are just too strong for me.
I can't keep up anymore.
I mean look what happened today.
You can't even trust me with your money
No point in keeping me around if
all I do is cause you trouble?
You don't want weak people
on your crew, do you?
Luffy, I still believe that you'll
be King of the Pirates one day.
But as for me, I'm just lucky.
I was able to make it this far
Even back when we first met
and I was gonna set off alone.
You probably just invited
me on your ship out of pity.
What are you talking about?
Get on already.
We're friends, right?
So get on!
That's the only reason I'm here.
There's no sense traveling together
if we don't even have the same goal!
Hey, Usopp, where are you going?
Wherever I go, it's my business.
It has nothing to do with you anymore.
Sorry, guys.
I'm leaving the crew.
This is goodbye.
Fine.
Have it your way, then.
Uthab!
Get back here!
It shouldn't be like this! Come
on! We can talk! Yeah! Come back!
I want you to stay!
Don't leave us!
Uthab, please!
Say something.
Luffy, I'm sorry I can't
follow you anymore.
And I'm sorry I was a
pain till the bitter end.
I know you're the captain of this
ship, so the Mary belongs to you.
That's why I want you to
fight me, Monkey D. Luffy.
I challenge you to a duel!
Huh?
Whoa, wait, what are you saying?
At 10 o 'clock tonight, I'll be back, so
you better be ready for a fight, Captain.
I can't stop you from
destroying your own ship,
but if I win, I'm taking
the Mary and leaving.
Either way, when we're done, the
last bond between us will be broken.